Masayoshi Oishi and
Airi Suzuki
Anissar Shamekas
It was a love house dession!
Who is the cutest of all?
Who?
It's Airi.
Thank you.
What's this?
Ishima, with all the talking glasses in the world of ani-song.
And...
I'm Airi Suzuki, the cutest of all!
Pleased to meet you.
Only Ayuri is allowed to do this.
Like this.
No, no, no.
Take this song.
They're raising the resistance bug.
That's for sure.
You know about this?
Of course I know it.
It's a big hit on TikTok.
That's the song from "The Last of Us", isn't it?
Yeah.
Does that mean
Does that mean that the idol will be here today?
It looks like it.
And Ayuri.
The other day's event
It was a great success, wasn't it?
It was a lot of fun.
No, it was...
That was great!
You finished on time!
That was perfect!
That was a close one!
The event is still being streamed in the archives.
Please take a look!
And...,
I heard that Airi will be covering the event this time.
That's right.
This time it's the opening theme for the second season of Bokoku no Kokoro no Yabasai Yatsura no Boku!
Atarayoso no Boku wa
I'll cover it.
Isn't this a very difficult song?
After I said I'd sing it, I took a look at it.
It's got a lot of lines.
That's right.
It's more my bad habit than anything else.
You don't have to put the title on it.
I'll do my best not to stop.
I see.
Well then, this time we have someone here to talk to you.
Yes!
I'm Aki Suda, aka Akichan from the "Lock on to Your Heart" super-toki-meki devotion club, super-toki-meki lemon.
Pleased to meet you.
She's so cute!
Speaking of Ms. Sugata, she is the cutest idol in 2022. But I've never heard that before,
I can see why people say that!
Yes, humble.
That's easy to be humble.
So cute!
A little too much smack.
You hit it too hard.
Like that.
I've recently opened a Tik-Tok on the show.
I'd like more people to know about my account, so I'd appreciate it if I could take a Tik-Tok with you.
Thank you very much.
The key is to wink at this point.
Close your mouth.
Oh my God, all kinds of things are coming out.
I'll let it all go.
Can you do this?
Flutter, flutter, flutter.
Organ, Yumiya, Wogun
Fotion, Fail.
5 Killer
Reach
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Last one, your eyes are asleep.
My eyes are starting to look like this.
I can do it now, if you want to laugh.
It's at an angle.
That's really good.
It looks good.
Finally, her eyes are asleep.
Let's do it again, this time.
Let's go to zero.
I'm going to look at all the cute things about the lovely idol Nozomi Sugai.
Thank you very much.
I'll teach you.
Let's start with Nozomi Sugai's cutest point number one.
She's an idol.
I was inspired by anime today!
Cute?
Cute!
Yes!
Cloud... can we see it a few times?
I'm so happy.
What's this all about?
Did you become an idol because of anime?
That's right.
Actually, the reason I wanted to become an idol
I wanted to be an idol because of an anime I saw in elementary school.
What kind of anime was it?
Jajan!
Pretty Rhythm.
Prism?
That's right.
What's so funny that you know about Prism?
It's an item where cute girls come out and sing, dance and perform
They sing, dance and perform at a skating rink.
Did you admire it? I guess so.
The world of Prism.
Yes, I love the main character, Ayla.
What do you like about her? What do you like about Ayla?
She's a bit of a tomboy.
But when it's time for the real thing, she's determined.
I like her because I'm attracted to her cool gap and her heroine-like personality.
So you're an anime fan, Mr. Suda?
I love anime.
What's wrong?
Elefruit... do you have any favorite works?
Rare Station Rudder That Day Tomorrow Rabbi brackets
I've been watching a lot of Riya Qu.
It's pretty shallow.
I also like action movies like Shinkou no Kyojin and that kind of thing.
And the last series.
I just finished it the other day.
It was great!
I was watching it on the plane.
I was watching it on the plane, and it matched up with Shinkou no Kyojin a little bit.
I was so moved that I felt like an emo
I was watching it as I boarded the plane.
How did you feel when you got off the plane?
It's not like this is the outside world.
That's funny.
No, it's not.
Thank you for watching this video.
It's funny!
You think it's funny?
You're ruining the fun!
I think it's funny!
It just keeps going and going! You'll see it again!
What's the second cutest thing you've ever done?
Can we see it again?
Why this!
I've never seen you use the camera like that!
You're doing that pitching thing, it's so cute!
There's still no storm!
I want to form Finite I.U. Am I cute?
Last one in Akita!
Yay!
We were forming "AiYu" and "AiYu".
It's a unit my friends and I started on our own because of Pretty Rhythm.
You didn't make your debut or anything?
We didn't debut, we just danced together on our own.
How did you come up with the name?
What's "I-You"?
I want to send you love and courage.
This is Anpanman.
He's cute.
It's funny.
What were you doing dancing in the entrance hall of our apartment building?
I like how that customer's brother is watching over him.
It's funny that even the superintendent of that heartwarming apartment came in and gave us something funny...
Garantia!
By the way, he did a lot of thinking.
He designed the costumes.
What's that?
I have a notebook where I wrote it down.
What?
From back then?
I've never shown it to you before.
Here it is.
For the first time!
Ta-da!
It's so cute!
Wait a minute.
I missed it.
I did it!
Ayu's debut
So cute!
Is that a costume written on the side of this?
The colors are written on it.
With hearts and feathers and stuff.
It's nice.
Are there more? There are more pages.
And then there's dancing and stuff written in letters.
What? Why?
Just a dance where you raise your right hand up and stuff like that.
Let's try this one.
Let's do it.
I've got it!
Hold hands and walk.
Left hand on the left
3. Right hand, right hand up
4. Left hand middle
5. Right hand middle
6. Middle facing up from bottom to top
Middle facing down and up
Big on the bamboo shoot!
7. Middle face up from bottom to top
Shake outside and inside with mother's fingers below the face
Oh, so cute!
So cute and cuddly!
One step in the middle, full to the left, full to the right, while turning the hand around
turn your hand once and then lower your head
9. turn your hand once and bow your head to the continuation of it
Eh, cute
Cute this
10. Lower your right hand down from the top and put both hands on top of each other in front of you
11. Bring your hands up and around
12. Wave your hands in front of your chest
13. Last.
Right hand up and down, left hand up and down, turn in front of you and do a piece
Yay
Yay!
I love it!
I'm confident for the first time.
Really? Did you see this?
No, I'm sorry, but I'm afraid that guarantee candy isn't enough for something like this.
It's not enough!
Ms. Suda, when she was in elementary school, she longed to be an idol.
I'd like to do something that idols are known for.
Then, Mr. Oishi, please make a cute announcement.
Oh, this?
Me?
Well, then...
The next cute point 3 is...
Okay, this is the button.
Sickle-cutter, sickle-cutter.
It's a sickle-cutter.
Why are you leaning forward?
I'm scared! I'm scared!
What's in the box?
Tsuda-san is so cute!
He didn't stop painting "What's in the box?
Now, let's have our idol guests try their hand at the usual "I wonder what's in the box?
Thank you very much!
Here's what we'll have Suda-san guess this time!
Aaaaaaah!
I seriously can't do this kind of thing.
Is it moving?
It's moving.
You mean it's alive?
Careful.
What do you think's in the box?
Yes. Excuse me.
It's moving, isn't it?
Be careful.
Oh, my God.
This is Chip.
No, surfing.
Solving.
Rain.
Oh, man!
This is awesome!
Action game!
Oh, my God! Open your mouth!
Let's go!
- Are you scared? You're not scared? You're not scared?
- Are you okay? Are you okay?
- Something's spinning!
- Are you getting used to it?
- Gross! You're gonna let it out?
- Are you gonna let it out?
- No!
- I made a mistake!
- No, it's not!
- What do you think it is? I'm telling you!
- I'm not a man!
- I made a mistake!
- I made a mistake! I made a mistake!
- You know...
Guess what's in the box.
Me.
I laughed the hardest in the history of the song.
I can't sing.
Okay, back to the question.
Can we go back?
I'm fine.
What's the fourth cutest thing about Brieve?
Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh.
He imitates a cicada.
What's that? What's that? What is that?
I'll do a cicada imitation.
Cute.
Then, shooter.
I get skirted at a noodle shop.
They say I'm a girl who can't sing. Am I cute?
Akitan shikakatan
Mimi mimi mimi mimi mimi
I left too much semitsunehata.
There's a lot of information on this one, too.
You were scouted at a ramen shop?
That's right.
I happened to be eating ramen with my whole family.
After that, we went to the dentist to go see a dentist.
While I was being treated, my father was being scouted.
That's where
I joined this office.
How is that possible?
I was so surprised.
He saw me eating ramen noodles.
I guess she looked beautiful eating ramen.
Is that so?
Going for ramen before work... that's pretty special, isn't it?
Don't you think?
That's for sure.
It's not like he's going for all-out ramen.
It's so annoying.
It's like, "Hurry up and set the table.
Here's your ramen.
Ramen!
And?
I joined the office. But you were considered a girl who couldn't sing?
I started to sing and dance for the first time when I was in the first year of junior high school, and that was the first time I really tried singing and dancing,
At that time, I had to sing a cappella at an audition, and I didn't know the rhythm or anything,
The big guys said, "Yes, go for it! Yes! Yes!
Yes! They were doing it all the time.
A cappella is the hardest part of the show.
I get so nervous.
In one recording session...
Oh! Here comes the girl who can't sing the best! It's like that.
It's painful! That's the kind of thing that stays with you.
I can't imagine what you'd look like now.
It must have taken a lot of effort.
How did you overcome it?
I had a lot of motivation.
I went through a lot of voice training and dance training.
I think I've managed to get to the point where I'm ready to show everyone what I'm capable of.
No, no, no, it's already amazing!
Everyone in TOKI sings so powerfully.
Each one of them has a different color.
They sing live at the concert.
That's right!
They're so great!
They sing live.
It's amazing!
It's because of her effort.
Next, Aki Suda's cute points!
Wait a minute!
Five.
I'd like to see Airi's version too.
I'm laughing so hard at the cicada I can't keep my voice down.
Oh, my God!
Come on...
No way! What should I do?
Suda-chan's cuteness point five is...
What do you think? Is that it?
Kitten's cute...
I'm going to imitate a cicada.
Mimimimimimimimimimi
I'll be dead in a week.
I'll die in a week I'm sorry
I'm getting cold with love
Suda-san, are you cute?
So cute.
Does that mean I'll be dead in a week?
I'm sorry.
Don't throw in that information about the cicadas.
You scared me.
And this is the most important point.
I'm becoming more like an idol.
Lately, I've been getting a lot of comments from people around me that I'm starting to look like an idol.
The way you walk and talk, you look like an idol.
I feel like an idol no matter where you take it out of my head.
In fact, Ms. Suda's staff told me
Mr. Suda's staff told me about an episode in which they thought he was becoming more and more like an idol.
What? Really?
You're here... for this?
What? I wonder...
It's a voice from the field.
It's like the fancier's body is ingrained in you.
When he thanked me, he made a heart symbol with his hand.
I've had people thank me while fangirling.
What? A staff member?
Yes.
If you ask him, he said he was doing the fancier's gesture completely unconsciously.
I thought that when he was expressing his feelings
It's like a funsur when you express your feelings.
I don't remember.
Cute.
Hey, what's this?
I'm playing the part of a staff member... and I'm trying to respond to something... so can I play?
I'm going to use the semi here today.
cUUUUUU ha
I still do it on a daily basis.
I do it.
I was doing it.
But you do too, don't you, Airi?
When you were an idol?
No, listen.
On this show.
A while ago...
When Q-taro was here.
He shook hands with a guy who made wakame seaweed that grows.
He said, "This is wakame that increases.
He said, "Please do wakame that increase.
I've been getting a lot of requests from people who saw the show
"Please do wakame that increases!" they say.
Is there a wakame seaweed revival?
And now, at 30 years old, these fans are having another wakame revival.
Oh my God!
It's because of what they did on this show!
It's bad!
There were three of them.
Aki-chan, do you know what a wakame seaweed grows?
Don't you have to ask?
I don't know.
You don't have to do it forever.
It's a trick by Airi Suzuki.
Look!
What did you do, Airi?
There's dried wakame seaweed.
If you soak dried wakame in water, it grows big.
It's just like that.
Wakame seaweed that grows
Don't sing anymore, I'm going home
Blue Jill...
Stop it, don't do this.
Why did I do this?
I'd like to ask my 18-year-old self.
Do you have anything like that?
It's like a one-hit wonder.
You're already known for this.
Suda, Suda, Suda. There's the Suda Dance.
I'm sorry.
There's too many Suda's.
A lot of Suda.
Suda, Suda, Suda, Suda, Suda, Suda, Suda, Suda, Suda, Suda, Suda.
Suda, Suda, Suda, Suda. It's Autumn!
Straw Whipped Autumn Chan
Suda Autumn.
Cute
I can push it
Suda Suda Suda It's Autumn
Straw sticky rice cake Autumn-chan
Why is there a straw sticky rice cake?
The food I used to love
You are so idolized!
I have the Kappa Dance too!
Kappa dance?
That's so sweet.
Why don't you go ahead and do it yourself?
Please, please, please, please.
Next.
Cheap to death
Just an endless dance
Oh!
The one-two-say
Gabba Gabba Gabba Gabba Gabba Gabba Gabba Gabba Pappa Pappa
Pappa pappa
Sorry.
I can't walk with my gloves on anymore.
Next up is this corner
I'll do my best.
This time, Sudasan will be covering an ani-song paper song, the end of the anime Heroine Taru no Nutsu Mono no Naka wa Ending Song by Honeyworks.
I don't know why I chose this song, but I really like the feeling of being a heroine, and I wanted to be a heroine too.
I chose this song because I love the feeling of being a heroine, and I wanted to be a heroine too.
I would like you to sing "Boku wa Boku wa" by Atarayo, the opening theme of the second season of "Boku no Kokoro no Yabayatsu".
Thank you very much!
It's a bad song!
When I heard this song, I thought it would be a good fit for Ailee...
I'm going to be the bad guy in someone's heart!
After the kappa dance?
Oh, no, don't do that.
Why did you choose this song, Suzua?
Well, I love Airi Suzuki's voice.
I'd love to hear Airi Suzuki in this song.
Thank you very much.
Now then, please give my best wishes to both of you.
Please listen to this song.
With Airi Suzuki, I'm
Heroine Nurturing Project at Suzua House
Thank you for your hard work